Guide to the Jobs With Justice Records 2001-2012
Jobs With Justice Records
- H4: Analia Penchaszadeh Files: Fundraising and Finance 2001-2007 (Box 32)
  - April 4, April 16, and Funder Mailing, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Foundation Proposal, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - General Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Sustainable Growth Initiative Contracts and Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Sustainable Growth Initiative Contracts, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Local Coalition Foundation Fundraising, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Louisville, Living Wage, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1997-2003 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - ACORN National Living Wage Campaign Training Conference, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    November 10 - 12 2000
  - Organizational Development, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Strategic Planning, 1991-2002 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Jobs with Justice Strategic Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Local Coalition Grants, CWA, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Local Coalition Prospects, 1996-1999 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Funding Requests, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Local Grants Process, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Utah, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - ESSN, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Boston Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Buffalo Fundraising, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Massachusetts Direct Mail, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    November - December 2000
  - Chicago, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Portland, 2001-2003 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Foundation Mailing, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    June 1999
  - Washington Direct Mail, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Kentucky Direct Mail, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Tucson, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    March 27 2001
  - Texas, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Vermont, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Florida Jobs with Justice, Unite for Dignity, 1999-2003 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Milwaukee, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - NYC Strategic Planning Retreat, 2001-2003 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Tenants' and Workers' Support Committee, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    Annual Report 1999
- H5: Analia Penchaszadeh Files: Fundraising and Finance 2001-2007 (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia, 2000-2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland Retreat, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    January 2001
  - Colorado, 2002-2004 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - District of Columbia Jobs with Justice, 2001-2003 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Jobs with Justice, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Indianapolis, Central Indiana, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Kentucky, 2000-2003 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Healthcare, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Healthcare, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Mapping Power, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Threshold Foundation, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - NAFFE, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - General Electric, 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - World Social Forum, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Fast Track, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - New Voices Media Project, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - World Social Forum, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Globalization, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - HC Inventories, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Healthcare, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Workers' Rights, 1994-2000 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Free Trade, FTAA Background, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - FTAA Media, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    April 21 2001
  - Global Justice Strategy Session, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Angelina Research Project, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - National Campaign for Jobs and Income Support, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Portland Workers' Rights, 2002-2004 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - International Human Rights, 2002-2004 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Portland, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Portland, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Jobs with Justice National Strategic Plan, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Justice for Janitors, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - General Electric, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Workers' Rights, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    Contains a framed photograph
  - Seattle, 2001-2003 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- H6: Analia Penchaszadeh Files: Fundraising and Finance 2001-2007 (Box 34)
  - New Mexico, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Contains a CD
  - New Economy, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous, 1999-2003 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Work Plan, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Voter Registration, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Portland Jobs with Justice and Workers' Rights Board, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Albany Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Portland Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Utah, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Salt Lake City, 1999-2003 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Denver, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Denver, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Colorado Jobs with Justice, 2002-2004 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Denver, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Eugene, 2000-2004 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Mid-Willamette Valley, 1999-2000 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Montana, Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- I1: Healthcare Files 1990s (Box 35)
  - Healthcare Action Week, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Clips, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    March 4 2004
  - Health Care, Makings, Visit Kit, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Healthcare Single Payer Survey, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Spring 1992
  - Old Healthcare, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Jobs with Justice Healthcare, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lobby Kit for Health Care (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Action Week, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    June 1994
  - Bad Bills Health Care (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Sign-On Letters Health Care, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Universal Healthcare Strategy Conference, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Jobs with Justice Healthcare, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - National Health Care Action Week, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    May 27 - June 7 1994
  - Jobs with Justice Mailings, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Jobs with Justice Healthcare, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Health Care Clips, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Jobs with Justice Health Care Reform, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Jobs with Justice Healthcare Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Jobs with Justice Healthcare Reform, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Jobs with Justice Healthcare, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Health Care Action Week, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    June 3 - 9 1991
  - Newspaper Clippings for Healthcare Protests, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Press Conference Call, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - The Emergency Drive for Healthcare, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Health Care Clips, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Health Care Clips, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- J1: Local Coalitions 2002-2009 (Box 36)
  - Chicago Staff, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Money, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Health Care Organizing Project, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland Money, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland, Ohio, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland Jobs with Justice Strategic Retreat, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland Health Care Organizing Project, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland Staff Search, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Susan Hagan, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Columbus, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Indianapolis Jobs with Justice, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Kentucky Money and Staffing, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Kentucky, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Milwaukee, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - South Bend, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Toledo, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - St. Louis, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - St. Louis Electoral, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - St. Louis Health Care Organizing Project, 2001-2003 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - St. Louis Fundraising, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Work Plans and Staff Meetings, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Fund Raising Meetings, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Staff Retreat, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    January 2004
  - Staff Retreat, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Reimbursements, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - UNITE Reimbursement STL, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - NTUI Tour, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Midwest Academy Training, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Money for Training on Site, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Applications, Money Training, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Money Training Prep, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Money Training Logistics, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Money Training, Session Designs (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - FACT, Kentucky, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - FACT Project, Training Tools, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - FACT Capacity Building, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - OCBR Training, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - OCBR Training Logistics, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Jobs with Justice Organizing and Collective Bargaining Rights Training, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    March 10 -13 2005
- J2: Local Coalitions 2002-2009; L. McSpedon Files (Box 37)
  - First Folder (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - AM Recruitment and Money Debrief, Midwest, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - AM Debrief, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Faith in Action Registration, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - AM Case Study Originals Faith in Action, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Faith in Action Gathering, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting Outreach and Host Committee, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Interfaith Service, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting 2005 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting 2005, J4J Breakfast (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Public Sector Pre-Conference, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meeting 2005, On Site (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - S and L Gathering Applications, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Staff and Leader Gathering, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting Scholarships, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meeting 2003 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Interfaith Service, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Field Retreat, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    November 2005
  - Yearly Local Coalition Development Goals, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Staff Meeting, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    April 2006
  - Work Reports, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Staff Meetings, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Reimbursements, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Staff Retreat, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    January 2006
  - Organizing Training Evaluation Executive Summary, Program Department, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Statewide Jobs with Justice, 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Walmart, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    Fall 2005
  - J4J Midwest, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Public Employee CB, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Peabody Campaign, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - SLAP Week of Action, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - HERE, Hotels, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - December 10 2005 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - 2005 Field Team (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Fundraising Meetings, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Work plans, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Staff Meetings, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Reimbursements, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Northeast Priorities, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Northeast Local Coalition Development Goals, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Northeast Information (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - SLAP Planning, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    August 2009
  - SLAP, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Strategic Planning, 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Training, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Training, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - FWF, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Building Jobs with Justice, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    September 2006
  - Building Jobs with Justice, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Jobs with Justice Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Women's Retreat Logistics and Essentials, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - FWF Buffalo and Rhode Island, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    August 2006
  - FWF, Buffalo, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Financial Management Training, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    May 2005
  - Right to Organize Materials, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Money Training Applications, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Money Training 2005 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - Women's Retreat, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- J3: L. McSpedon Files; Press Hits 2004-2005 (Box 38)
  - Women's Retreat Follow-Up, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Women's Retreat Follow-Up, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Women's Retreat, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky-Mexico Worker Exchange, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - IRS Group Exemption, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Wal-Mart Stuff, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Good Jobs First, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Action Week Information, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Health Care Action Week Report, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    October 2004
  - Miscellaneous Jobs with Justice Samples, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Innovative Strategies, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Economic Development Pre-Conference, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meeting Scholarships, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting, Debrief and Follow-Up, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Important Annual Meeting Documents, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Verizon, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Verizon, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Verizon Wireless, 2005-2007 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Unsolicited Media Requests, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    May - September 2005
  - Clippings, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    November - December 2005
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Regional Clippings, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    January - April 2005
  - Regional Clippings, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    May - July 2005
  - Regional Clippings, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    August - December 2005
- K1: JwJ Planning Committee (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous Jobs with Justice Documents, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - JWJ Presidents Council Meeting, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    January 29 1998
  - Planning Committee, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    July 18 - 20 1998
  - Planning Committee Meeting, Food and Logistics, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Planning Committee Materials, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Planning Committee Logistics, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    November and December 1998
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    July 12 - 14 1997
  - Snapshots, Surveys, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Jobs with Justice Planning, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Local Coalition Planning Guide, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Planning Resources, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Oregon Planning Examples, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Cleveland Planning Retreat, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Washington Planning Retreat, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Washington State Retreat, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    November 1996
  - Planning Committee, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Planning Committee, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Jobs with Justice Retreat, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Jobs with Justice Proposed Calendar of Meetings, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Retreat Meeting, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Retreat Meeting, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - June Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    June 8 and 9 2000
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Planning Committee Materials, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Jobs with Justice Planning Committee Meeting, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    November 5 - 7 1999
  - Planning Committee, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Planning Committee 1999 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Planning Committee, Various Documents, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Planning Committee Materials, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    November 1999
- K2: JwJ Planning Committee cont.; National Days of Action (Box 40)
  - Billy Bragg and the Blokes, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Welfare, Day of Action, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Healthcare Jobs with Justice, 1993-1995 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Budget Chart, BB, 1999-2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Concert Tour, 1994-1999 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Stop Corporate Greed, Jobs with Justice, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - BB King Blues Festival, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - FTAA, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Health Care Action Week, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Wal-Mart, UFCW, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Press Clips, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Alphabetical by Paper
  - FTAA Local Actions, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Alphabetical by State
  - FTAA, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - September 26 2000 "S26" (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - April 16 Rally "A16", 2000 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - "A16" Press Clips, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - SLAP Day of Action, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    April 4 2000
  - SLAP National Student Labor Day of Action, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - April 4 2002 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - April 4 2000 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Jobs with Justice Presentations, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    Contains Slideshow slides
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- K3: National Days of Action (Box 41)
  - NPP Report Press Clips, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - NPP Report Release, Sign Orders for December 8, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - NPP Report Release, Release Cities Conference Call, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - NPP Report and Requests, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Town Hall Meetings, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Briefing RSVP, NPP Report Release, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - December 8 Report Release, Media Reports, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO, Right-to-Organize Day of Action, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    June 24 1998
  - Gannett Actions, Local Contracts, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Gannett Day of Action Press Clips, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    June 12 1997
  - Gannett Day of Action Follow-Up, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Sprint Actions, Press Clips, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - SPRINT Actions Coordinators, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Sprint Actions, Literature, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - "Grin" and Contacts, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    Title partially illegible. June 12 1997
  - Sprint, 1994-1997 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - June 12 Day of Action, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - "All We Wanted was a Union" Sprint Actions, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - CWO, Bell Atlantic and Verizon Campaign, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Verizon Information, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - National Day of Action Corporate Greed, Coordinators List Forms, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Day of Action Corporate Greed, Event Reports, Media, Etc., 1996 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Bill of Rights, Day of Action, Organizing Kit (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - June Day of Action, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Health Care Action Day, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    February 17 1994
  - Health Care Action Day, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    October 3 1990
  - Healthcare News Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Helena Labs, CWA, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Jobs with Justice Press Clippings and Materials, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Helena Labs, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - "Working Hard, Earning Less", 1997 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - "Working Hard, Earning Less: The Story of Jobs Growth in America", 1998 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    State-by-State Reports. December 8 1998
  - Day of Action Media Plan, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - "Working Hard, Earning Less: The Story of Job Growth in America", 1998 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    December 8 1998